{
  "extraDescription": "E.g. square of 3 is represented as \\(3^2\\), and is equal to \\(3 \\times 3\\), i.e. multiplication of 3 by itself, and not \\(3 \\times 2\\)",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(6^2\\)",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12^2\\)",
      "answer": "144"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10^2\\)",
      "answer": "100"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8^2\\)",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11^2\\)",
      "answer": "121"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2^2\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(9^2\\)",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1^2\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(14^2\\)",
      "answer": "196"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(15^2\\)",
      "answer": "225"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4^2\\)",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(16^2\\)",
      "answer": "256"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(20^2\\)",
      "answer": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(13^2\\)",
      "answer": "169"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0^2\\)",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(17^2\\)",
      "answer": "289"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(18^2\\)",
      "answer": "324"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5^2\\)",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3^2\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7^2\\)",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(19^2\\)",
      "answer": "361"
    }
  ]
}
